DIDRIK H. LINDBERG

Address: 66 Ocean View Avenue, Santa Barbara, 93103 California USA

Phone: (805) 284-7556

Email: lindberg.didrik@gmail.com | LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/didrik-lindberg-3b2955148/

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Currently seeking to establish an internship during my junior year (2020). I am a full-time international college student at San Francisco State University where I am pursuing a bachelor's degree in Economics. Since I started college I have continuously been working to gain experience within my field of career. The summer of 2019 I was working in the Office of international education at Santa Barbara City college, and the previous summer I was working a summer internship position in a financial auditor branch under the Swedish government. I would like to utilize my acquired skills and develop additional knowledge in the area of financial analytics and management.

CAREER OVERVIEW

Santa Barbara City College - Administrative assistant & Peer Advisor

2019-2020

Dealing with classified information, scheduling appointments, applying my knowledge to assist
prospective students through the processes of admission to graduation and general questions
about school and visas. Administrative tasks.

Malmo Kommun - Auditor Officer

Summer 2018

◆ Analyzed annual financial statements of government contractors that oversee persons of disabilities financials. Made final decision of approval or revision, with full authority to accept or revise requested fees under the associated law.

Sinclair Community College - *International student ambassador*

2017 - 2018

- Administrative office tasks which often dealt with classified information regarding international student documents. Navigating new students through the processes of admission, graduation, transferring and general questions about school and visas.
- Started the "International student soccer club" by recruiting players and acquiring funding from the school government.

Bilklick SE - In-house salesman

2016 - 2017

• Created basic excel formulas and formats for the sales team leaders and helped develop new business strategies to increase company's top line revenue through mitigating company expenses by streamlining business operations and processes.

Additional Experience	
Au Pair Exchange Program, New York NY Surf & kayak instructor, Santa Barbara CA	2015-2016 2018-2019
Education History	
Sinclair Community College AS-T - Business administration	2017–2018
Santa Barbara City College AD-T - Economics AS Science-Math	2018- 2019